Amanda Steele Show.
Cryrese is...
Cryrese, I see what you did there.
Tyrese is basically a personifying, yet again, why they should have never gave everybody social media.
Okay, he posted a video of a Latino family doing like family-oriented things.
And in his caption, decided to big them up while demeaning the entire Black race.
He said, sometimes I wish I was born Latino.
I mean, the Latin community is grounded in family, loyal, entrepreneurs, businessmen.
I have no idea how we lost our way.
The majority of us is Black men and the millions are locked up in prison.
I could take my time here to explain to you why this is complete nonsense.
But I just feel like I should actually do the opposite and add to the nonsense.
Since Tyrese wants so bad to be a part of the Latin community, we say, you know what?
We're going to help you get there and Latinize your music.
He has a song lately.
Have I told you I love you?
Let's translate it.
You see where I'm going with this?
Now, of course, remember, I am not a member of the Latinx community, but I'm just giving
him some inspiration.